# **Katherine Adams**

## Certified Nursing Assistant (CNA) - Public Partnerships

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Katherine-Adams/22472e9069b5690e

My professional experience has been working with the elderly as far as assisting them with their everyday living bathing, dressing, eating and medication reminders.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Certified Nursing Assistant (CNA)**

Public Partnerships - November 2011 to January 2013

Provided assistance in doing tasks related to individual care;

- Assisted in meal preparation, housekeeping and laundry;
- Transported individual to appointments and community activities;
- Monitored and assisted individual to receive appropriate health care;
- · Administer medication.

### **CNA**

Jevs - Philadelphia, PA - October 2009 to January 2011

Helping clients with assistance with everyday needs.. meal prep, medication reminder...

### **EDUCATION**

Star Career Academy January 2013 to March 2013

Edison High School September 1984 to June 1985

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- · Certified in CNA, OSHA, Phlebotomy and CPR
- Knowledge of specimen, blood and urinalysis collection
- Highly motivated employee that takes initiative.
- Effective customer service skills.
- · Good Communication and organizational skills.
- · Learns new skills quickly.